You@This feels so good.
Shirley@Do you like it?
You@I love it.
You@You're so good at this.
Shirley@Do you want to go faster?
Shirley@Or slower?
You@I like both.
You@That's my sensitive spot.
Shirley@Slowly...
You@Every time your hands rub like that, it feels so warm.
Shirley@Warm feeling?
You@It's getting so swollen.
You@I didn't expect you to be this naughty in private.
Shirley@Only in bed.
You@No wonder you design such kinky clothes.
Shirley@That's my fetish.
You@I love you like this.
You@You're so naughty, deliberately touching my sensitive spots.
Shirley@So...
Shirley@This is how men's parts are like.
You@I can't take it anymore.
You@Go faster for me.
Shirley@Faster...
You@It feels so good.
You@It feels so good to be rubbed by your hands like this.
Shirley@Do you like it?
Shirley@Do you want it even warmer?